Now I'm ready to put the images onto our sheet of plastic.
The piece of plastic that we're using is a thick piece of plastic, but it's a bit translucent, so you can see through, and it will be perfect for getting the images, placing the sheet of paper underneath and getting the images to show through so that we can go ahead and trace it onto the sheet of plastic.
So I'll go ahead and do that.
First I want to get the right size of my plastic, and I'm going to cut it to about twenty four to thirty inches long.
So I cut off the excess, and then put the plastic over the sheet of paper with my images that I drew, and I'm going to only use the pencil at this point, I'm not going to start using any kind of permanent markers yet.
But I'm going to draw directly onto the plastic where I saw the images, where the images just come through on the bottom, and I move the plastic around from place to place so I can get images on different angles and on different locations of the plastic.
It doesn't have to look exactly the way it looked on the paper, those are just my original images that I want to apply to the plastic, but not in the same exact place.
It's much easier to draw the images on the plastic by using this white paper underneath, because when you draw on the plastic, this plastic sheet that we're using, you don't see the images, you can't really see the pencil so clearly.
So it's a lot easier to have the image underneath and then just trace around it so you don't have to worry about which lines you made and what lines you didn't make, because sometimes you made a line and you don't see it so clearly.
And we just move the plastic around, making sure that most of the areas are covered with some type of image.
Don't overcrowd the plastic with images, but, then again, don't leave any large open blank spaces.
You might want to hold up the plastic sheet every once in a while just to get a clear look at where you've placed your images and which spaces are still left empty.
And also you might want to fold it up just also to see where the fasteners are going to go so you know where to put an image; you don't want to cut off an image underneath the fold.
So, just to get a clear look, it's good to stop every once in a while and just take a look at the sheet of plastic and see where your images are lying.
So now I've shown you how to take the images and put them onto the sheet of plastic, using the original white paper, the original white images, that we drew.